你好，我是 Bob Tabor。在这个系列的视频中
Hi I'm Bob Tabor and in this series of videos,
一共 75 部视频
over 75 videos,
我会演示如何构建
I'm going to demonstrate how to build apps
可以在 Windows Store 上售卖或者免费下载的应用
that can be sold or downloaded for free on the Windows Store
这些应用为 Windows 桌面和手机而设计
for Windows desktop, or phone,
以及任何可以使用 Universal Windows Platform 应用的地方
or wherever Universal Windows Platform apps can be used.
很快就会包括 Xbox One
Which will soon include devices like the Xbox One,
Microsoft Hub 甚至 HoloLens 等设备
Microsoft Hub, and even the HoloLens.
我所说的 Universal Windows Platform
Now that term Universal Windows Platform I just used
指的是一系列工具和 API
it describes tools and APIs that you can utilize
你可以用它们来构建应用从而运行在各种
to build apps that run universally
全新的 Windows 设备上
across all new Windows devices.
好处就是你可以只编写一个应用程序
And the beauty is that you can write one application
然后在各种屏幕分辨率上看起来都很好
and it'll look great on many different screen resolutions
在各种设备类型上也是
and device form factors.
这也是我在这一系列视频中
And really that's one of the most important things
将要讨论和演示的
that I'm going to discuss and demonstrate
最重要的一点
in this series of lessons.
这一系列视频是为纯粹的新手
So this series is intended for an absolute
而设计的
beginner audience.
就算这么说，你也应当对 C# 和 Visual Studio
Having said that, you should already have some familiarity
有一点了解
with C# and Visual Studio.
我也希望你是在确保自己看过了
And I want to assume that you're watching this after
Channel 9 的 Microsoft 虚拟学院里的
making sure that you've either watched or at least
为新手设计的 C# 基础系列课程或者至少了解
you understand all the concepts that I discuss in
我在其中讨论的概念之后
the C# fundamentals for absolute beginners series
再来观看这一系列的视频
on Microsoft Virtual Academy in channel nine.
这就是那个课程的 URL
You can find it at this URL on the screen.
如果你已经是一个经验丰富的开发者
Now if you're already an experienced developer
那么——合理地警告一下——说实话
then -- fair warning -- quite honestly here,
这门课程的进度对你来说可能会太过缓慢
this course is going to move very slow for you.
我们是有意放慢速度的
And we did that on purpose.
说真的，应该会有更好的资源
And honestly there's probably some better resources
让你可以不这么浪费时间
out there where you can spend your time.
我推荐你去看 Andy Wigley 和 Shen Chauhan
I'd recommend that you watch Andy Wigley and Shen Chauhan
创建的一个系列视频
in a series that they created called
叫做 Windows 10 开发者向导
a developers guide to Windows 10.
讲得很好，内容新，总之是个很好的视频
Great, up to date, it's awesome.
如果你是个很有经验的开发者的话
And I'd recommend you start there
我推荐你从那里开始
if you're already an experienced developer.
我所创建的这个视频系列
Now this is the fourth version of this particular video
这已经是第四个版本了
series that I've created.
我从 Windows Phone 7 开始
And I started way back on the Windows Phone 7
那是在 2009 或者 2010 年
in about 2009 / 2010.
每次我发布一个新版本的系列视频
Each time that I release a version of this series
我都会被翻来覆去地问一些问题
I'm asked a few questions repeatedly.
所以我要在一开始就回答一下
So I want to answer those right up front
从而消除误解
so that there's no misunderstanding.
首先，你必须用 Windows 10
First of all, you must use Windows 10
来为 Windows 10 构建应用
to build apps for Windows 10,
以及构建 Universal Windows Platform 应用
to build Universal Windows Platform apps.
你不能用 Windows 8.1 或者 Windows 8
You cannot use Windows 8.1, or Windows 8,
或者 Windows 7、Windows XP
or Windows 7, or Windows XP.
你必须用 Windows 10，这是第一点
Alright, you have to use Windows 10, that's number one.
第二点，你必须用 Visual Studio 2015
Number two, you have to use Visual Studio 2015.
我推荐你使用
Now I recommend that you use
Visual Studio 2015 社区版
Visual Studio 2015 Community Edition,
这是个免费的版本，具有专业版所有的功能
which is a free edition with all the features of Pro edition
但是它是专为用于学习用途或者
but it's intended for individuals who are just learning
要创建一个基于社区的项目的人而设计的
or creating a community based projects.
坦率地说你可以用其他版本的 Visual Studio
Now frankly you can use other editions of Visual Studio
但不是之前的版本
but not previous versions.
你必须用 2015 版来构建
You must use version 2015 to build
Universal Windows Platform 应用，这是第二点
Universal Windows Platform apps, that's number two.
第三，你将会看到我使用手机模拟器
Number three, you're going to see me use the phone emulator
从而时不时地运行和测试我的程序
in order to run and test my applications occasionally.
它看起来像是一个运行在屏幕上的小手机
It'll look like a little phone running on my screen
在右手边有一个菜单
with a little menu off to the right hand side.
实际上它运行的是一个叫做 Hyper-V 的软件
It's actually running software called Hyper-V
那是一个用于在桌面上运行虚拟机
which is a platform for running virtual machines
的平台
on your desktop.
因此它是在一个小的、看起来像是个手机的虚拟机里
And so it's running the Windows Phone 10 operating system
运行着 Windows Phone 10 操作系统
in a little virtual machine that looks like a phone.
你或许需要使用特殊的硬件
Now you might need special hardware
来运行这个手机模拟器
to run the phone emulator.
具体地，你的主板和芯片必须支持
Specifically your motherboard and your chip
一个叫 SLAT 的技术
must support a technology called SLAT,
全名叫做二级地址转换
or rather "Second Level Address Translation".
大多数现代的主板都支持这个技术
Now most modern motherboards will support this,
但是并不是所有的主板和芯片都支持
however not all motherboards and chips support this.
更重要的是，我帮不上什么忙
Most importantly, I can't help you with this.
我对这个了解非常少
I understand very little about it.
如果你在安装 Visual Studio 2015 时遇到了错误
If you get errors during install of Visual Studio 2015
你可以在微软的论坛里寻求帮助
then you can search Microsoft's forums for help,
但是再重复一遍，我帮不了你
but again I can't help you.
过去我曾经试过去帮忙，但是坦率地讲
I've tried to help in the past and honestly I've
我误导的人恐怕比我真正帮到的人更多
probably confused more people than I've actually helped.
如果你不能在电脑上运行模拟器
Now the worst case scenario if you can't get
最坏的情况可能是
the emulator running on your local machine,
你需要在一部运行着 Windows Phone 10
is that you might need to deploy your apps
完全版或者测试版的手机上
to a physical phone device running
部署你的应用
either the full edition or a beta edition of Windows
从而用来测试
Phone 10 for the purpose of testing.
方法很简单
It's simple to do,
但是在这一系列视频里
however I don't demonstrate how to do that
我不会演示如何去做
in this series of videos.
网上有很多文章介绍了具体的方法
There are articles online that'll show you how.
如果上面的要求你都满足
Now if you have all these things in place
那么第四点，你需要去打开
then, number four, you're going to need to
开发人员模式
turn on Developer Mode.
方法是打开 Windows 10 的设置
And the way that you get that is you open up Settings
然后打开更新和安全
in Windows 10 and you go to Update & Security.
在左边选择针对开发人员
And then on the left hand side you select For Developers,
确保你选中了开发人员模式
and make sure to choose Developer mode.
如果它要求你保存，那么就保存
And if it asks you to save then go ahead and save.
我不太确定，记不清楚了
I'm not sure, I can't remember that particular part.
但是一定要确保你打开了开发人员模式
But make sure that you have that set.
如果你没有设置好的话
Visual Studio will probably give you an error
Visual Studio 恐怕会在你第一次运行程序时
if you first run an application if you don't
报一个错误，OK？
have that setting set up, okay?
这一系列的视频
Now this series of videos
长度一共有 15 到 16 个小时，非常地详尽
is about 15 or 16 hours long, it's fairly comprehensive.
这一系列最重要的新特性是
And one of the most important new features
我会给你布置一些作业
of this training series is that I'm going to give you
叫做挑战
homework assignments called challenges.
我会给你用来按要求构建应用
And I'll give you all the tools that you need
所需要的全部工具
to build an app to my specifications
我甚至用一个视频的形式给你
and then I'm even going to give you the solution
所有挑战的解决方案
to the challenge in the form of a video
从而避免你卡壳
in case you get stuck.
对你来说这是个好方法
And that's a great way for you,
你应该去做做这些挑战
and you should definitely do these challenges
就像我喜欢说的那句话
where you "get your hands dirty in the code"
写写代码练练手
as I like to say it.
我们还会做一个小的备忘条
We're also going to build a little cheat sheet
从而用来回顾
for review purposes,
你可以在你完成了这一系列的视频之后
and then you can reference it after you finish
用来参考
the series of videos.
在你开始着手构建你自己的程序时
Feel free to add to the cheat sheet
你可以把你认为有用的任何东西
anything that you think might be useful
添加到备忘条上
as you go forward and start building your own applications.
在系列的后半部分
And then finally in the last half of the series,
我们会构建四个完整的应用程序
we're going to build four entire applications
其中有一个还会添加到 Windows Store
and even one of them for inclusion in the Windows Store.
这些应用用来向你展示
Now these apps are going to show you
如何像一个应用开发者一样思考
how to think like an app developer
从概念开始直到实现
from concept through implementation.
我们会用许多不同的技术和 API
And we'll use a variety of different techniques, and APIs,
以及工具和方法，来学习如何
and tools and approaches to learn how to
与设备上的传感器进行交互
interact with sensors on a given device.
如何访问媒体库
How to access media libraries,
如何访问提供天气更新的在线服务
how to access online services that provide weather updates.
甚至可以让你接触一些有趣的服务
And even allow us to tap into fun services
例如漫威漫画的在线 API
like Marvel comics web API,
可以获取到所有角色的信息
that allow us to retrieve back all their characters
以及他们的艺术作品
and look through them and look through the artwork.
这一系列里的许多视频都会带有一个 zip 文件
Now many of the videos in the series will have a zip file
其中包括我在录制视频时所写的
associated with them that contains the code
所有的代码
that I wrote while recording the video.
或者在刚才我所提到的
Or in the case of challenges like I just described
挑战里
a moment ago,
会包含你需要用到的图像和说明
it'll contain the images that you need, any instructions,
以及其他所有用于完成一项挑战的
or any other files that'll be required
各种各样的文件
in order to actually perform that challenge.
文件都会在你现在观看视频
Now the file will be on the page
或者你最初下载视频
where you're currently watching the video,
的页面上
or where you originally downloaded the video from.
所以在你在评论里提问
So please before you ask in the comments,
我找不到下载链接
"I can't find the download link,
下载链接在哪，下载链接！
where's the download link, the download link!"
在这之前，请在浏览器里按下键盘上的 Ctrl + F
Please hit Control + f on your keyboard in your web browser
搜索关键词 download
and search for the term "download".
如果找不到对应文件的链接
If there's no link to download a file
那么这个视频可能没有可下载的文件
then that particular video does not have files to download.
请先用关键词 download 搜索一下
Please search for the term download first.
尽管这是一个内容非常丰富的视频系列
Now while this is a very inclusive set of videos
我是说，15 到 16 小时的内容非常之多
I mean 15 to 16 hours is a lot of content to go through.
这还仅仅是个介绍
This is still really just an introduction.
我不可能向你展示 Universal Windows Platform
I can't possibly show you everything
所包含的全部内容
that the Universal Windows Platform contains.
你只应该把这个当成一个入门介绍
You should treat this as a gentle introduction only,
你还应该去参考
but you should always refer back to
Windows 开发人员中心里微软自己的文档
Microsoft's own documentation at the Windows Dev Center
从而对如何使用 Universal Windows Platform 的全部内容
for comprehensive explanation
得到详尽的解释
how to get the most out of Universal Windows Platform.
你可以从 http://dev.windows.com 访问到
And you can access that at http://dev.windows.com
记住，你不能用像是看电影
Now remember that you can't just watch
或者像看电视那样的方式
a screen cast tutorial training series
来看完这一系列的视频
the way that you would watch a movie or a sitcom on TV.
你必须成为一个积极的学习者
You're going to need to become an active learner.
不要害怕倒回来重看整个视频
Don't be afraid to rewind or even rewatch an entire video
或者其中的一小段
or a portion of the video if at first
如果有什么东西一开始没让你完全理解的话
something doesn't really make a lot of sense to you.
或者从我给你的链接访问 Windows Dev Center
Or look at the documentation at the Windows Dev Center
的开发文档
at the link I just shared with you
从而得到关于我们在视频中
for more details surrounding the given topic
讨论的一个话题的更多信息
that we're discussing at that moment in the videos.
当你用各种不同的方法来学习
You learn best whenever you use different
同一个内容时，你才能学得最好
modalities to learn the same idea, the same content.
我所提供的视频只是让你
And ultimately the videos that I'm presenting are just
用来实现你构造在 Windows Store 中销售的应用
one tool to help you realize your aspirations
这个愿望的一个工具
of building apps for sale in the Windows Store.
如果你个人喜欢我在这里所做的工作
Now, on a personal note if you like what I do here
请访问我的网站
please visit me at
http://www.LearnVisualStudio.NET
我在那里帮助新手得到他们的
where I help beginners get their
第一份软件开发工作
first software development job
在世界最好的公司中
building Windows and web apps
构建 Windows 和 Web 应用
into world's best companies.
那里有各种各样的挑战
There are tons of challenge exercises there
以及对使用 Visual Studio、C# 和 ASP.NET 以及其他工具
and deeper insights into writing software using
编写软件的更加深刻的内容
Visual Studio, and C#, and ASP.NET and more.
好的，现在我要花点时间来感谢
Alright now finally I'd like to take a moment and thank
观看过这一系列前几个版本的
the hundreds of thousands of people who have watched
成百上千的观众们
the previous versions of this series.
以及对那些花了点时间告诉微软
And for those who took the time to actually tell Microsoft
你们需要更多类似这样的培训的人们
that you wanted more of this type of training.
是你们的反馈带来了这套最新的视频
Your feedback made this happen,
非常感谢
so thank you very much.
我还要感谢 Andy Wigley，他认真地回答了
Also I want to thank Andy Wigley who patiently answered
我的各种问题，还在我录制这一系列视频时
all of the questions that I had and gave me a ton of advice
给了我各种各样的建议
while I was building this series.
我非常感谢他在我创建这些课程时
I'm very thankful for his guidance
给我的指导
as I worked on these lessons.
最后，这一系列视频主要是在
And ultimately this series was championed primarily
Clint Rutkas 的支持下才得以出现的
by Clint Rutkas who has been involved in almost all of the
他参与了几乎我为微软所做的所有视频节目
video projects that I have worked on for Microsoft.
没有 Clint，不会有这些视频
Without Clint, none of this would be possible.
所以请在 Twitter 上关注他
So please reach out to him on Twitter
让他知道你对他工作的赞赏
and let him know how much you appreciate his good work.
好了，准备工作到此结束
Okay so enough setup.
你在 Windows 10 上安装了 Visual Studio 2015
You've got Visual Studio 2015 running on Windows 10
也在设置里打开了开发人员模式
and you've turned on Developer mode in Settings
就像刚才我们看到的那样
like we looked at just a moment ago,
你现在在想接下来会是什么内容
and you're wondering what comes next.
我们将会从下一个视频正式开始学习
Well we're going to get started in the very next video.
下期再见
We'll see you there.